Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ nguyenmanhdung (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

.NET Core

DevOps

Microsoft SQL Server

Languages

English

Nguyen Manh Dung

Software Engineer at MISA JSC

Quận Cầu Giấy, Hanoi, Vietnam

Summary

I have over 6 years of experience, I'm a skilled .NET backend developer. For over 4 years, I have focused my expertise on developing large-scale enterprise applications. I possess a strong understanding of development processes and the latest technologies. While my primary focus is Backend, I'm also familiar with DevOps principles and tools such as Jenkins, Harbor, Helm, ArgoCD, Docker, Kubernetes, etc. Additionally, I have some experience with front-end technologies such as Vue.js, Angular.

Experience

MISA JSC

4 years 10 months

Senior Software Engineer

June 2020 - Present (4 years 10 months)

Cầu Giấy, Hanoi, Vietnam

At MISA, I participated in various projects, including the development of projects for both individual users and enterprises.

DevOps Engineer

October 2023 - July 2024 (10 months)

Cầu Giấy, Hanoi, Vietnam

Nhật Cường Software

Software Developer

April 2019 - May 2020 (1 year 2 months)

Thanh Xuân, Hanoi, Vietnam

At Nhat Cuong Software, I was a core member of the development team for the appointment management, health record, and backend development for the Hanoi Smart City application.

TechFox JSC Software Developer August 2019 - April 2020 (9 months) Nam Từ Liêm, Hanoi, Vietnam

At TechFox JSC, I was a software developer responsible for the development and maintenance of the .NET Core backend for a Content Management System (CMS) project for a large corporation in Vietnam.

30Shine JSC.

.NET Developer

August 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 8 months)

At 30Shine, I participated in the design, development, and maintenance of their core applications, including ERP, CMS, and the booking system on 30shine.com. I joined 30Shine as a fresher and later advanced to the role of a junior developer during my time working there.

GAFIM.,JSC Software Development Apprentice July 2015 - July 2017 (2 years 1 month) Đống Đa, Hanoi, Vietnam

Education

Aptech Learning

Advanced Diploma In Software Engineering, Computer Software Engineering · (2019 - 2021)

IMIC Technology

Certification in C# and ASP.NET MVC programming, Computer Programming/ Programmer, General · (2016 - 2017)